Can you stomach it?
Feed is a mystery, thriller film directed by Brett Leonard.
A cybercrime investigator tracks a man suspected
of force-feeding women to death.
Michael Carter, played by Alex O'Loughlin.
Phillip Jackson, played by Patrick Thompson.
Deidre, played by Gabby Millgate.
Richard, played by Jack Thompson.
Nigel, played by Matthew Le Nevez.
Father Turner, played by David Field.
Feed is a 2005 Australian body horror crime film directed by Brett Leonard.
The plot involves a police investigation of the paraphilia known as feederism.
The film explores themes of overweight, detective, sociopath, obesity, internet.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.